let data = [
	{
		question: "7 + 7",
		answer: "14"
	},

	{
		question: "9 + 9",
		answer: "18"
	},

	{
		question: "37 + 43",
		answer: "80"
	},
	
	{
		question: "39 + 71",
		answer: "110"
	},
	
	{
		question: "20 + 10",
		answer: "30"
	},

	{
		question: "60 + 97",
		answer: "157"
	},

	{
		question: "1 + 1",
		answer: "2"
	},
	{
		question: "7 + 7",
		answer: "14"
	},

	{
		question: "9 + 9",
		answer: "18"
	},

	{
		question: "37 + 43",
		answer: "80"
	},
	
	{
		question: "39 + 71",
		answer: "110"
	},
	
	{
		question: "20 + 10",
		answer: "30"
	},

	{
		question: "60 + 97",
		answer: "157"
	},

	{
		question: "1 + 1",
		answer: "2"
	},
	
	{
		question: "selesai"
	},


	
];

export {data};